Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
MS 377
Miller, Tom
Collection consists of the papers of Tom Miller and underground press publications collected by him. The Publications by Tom Miller series includes articles, correspondence, manuscripts, and research materials relating to his books. The Research Files series contains a variety of materials on a broad range of topics. Materials within each file are arranged by format (correspondence, research material, and notes). Items within each of these subdivisions are then arranged chronologically.
40 Linear Feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None
Biographical Note
Tom Miller is a noted writer of literature on the Southwest and Latin America. For over thirty years Miller has been producing books, articles, and commentary on topics ranging from Panama hats to the song La Bamba. His nine books include Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink: Offbeat Travels through America's Southwest; On The Border; The Panama Hat Trail; Trading with the Enemy: A Yankee Travels Through Castro's Cuba; and Writing on the Edge: A Borderlands Reader. His articles have been published in such magazines as the Washington Post, New York Times, Smithsonian, and Rolling Stone. Miller was a founder of the U.S.-Cuba Writers Conference, a bilingual and bi-national conference held in Havana, and is also a cofounder of Writers of the Americas. Tom Miller has been affiliated with the University of Arizona's Latin American Area Center since the 1990s and was a visiting lecturer in creative writing for the university in the 1980s. Miller was awarded the Lowell Thomas Gold Award for best travel book of the year in 2001 for Jack Ruby's Kitchen Sink: Offbeat Travels through America's Southwest. He also was awarded a Gilder Lehrman fellowship from Gilder Lehrman Institute of American History in 2002. He resides in Tucson, Arizona with his wife Regla Albarrán.
Organization
This collection is organized into six series
I. Publications by Tom Miller
II. Research Files
III. Personal Materials
IV. Salt of the Earth (film)
V. Manuscripts by Other Authors
VI. Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera.
Scope and Content Note
Collection consists of the papers of Tom Miller and underground press publications collected by him. The Publications by Tom Miller series includes articles, correspondence, manuscripts, and research materials relating to his books. The Research Files series contains a variety of materials on a broad range of topics. Materials within each file are arranged by format (correspondence, research material, and notes). Items within each of these subdivisions are then arranged chronologically. The personal Materials series includes materials on Miller's teaching career. The Salt of the Earth series contains extensive documentation on this film about striking New Mexico miners, which was created by blacklisted professionals from the Hollywood film industry. The Manuscripts by Other Authors series consists of writings by Christopher Baker, William Lee Brent, and Adam Kufield. The Underground Press, Miscellaneous Publications, and Ephemera series is alphabetized by title and includes; comics, leaflets, and magazines. Most of the files in this collection retain their original headings put in place by Miller.
Miller, Tom, 1947- -- Archives.; Baker, Christopher P., 1955- -- Manuscripts.; Brent, William Lee, 1930- -- Manuscripts.; Kufeld, Adam -- Manuscripts.; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Archives.; Travelers' writings.; Hat trade -- Ecuador.; Hat trade -- United States.; American literature -- Southwestern States.; American literature -- Mexican-American Border Region.; Short stories, American -- 20th century.; American fiction -- 20th century.; Mexican-American Border Region -- Literary collections.; Mexican literature -- Mexican-American Border Region.; Southwestern States -- Literary collections.; Arizona -- Description and travel.; Cuba -- Description and travel.; Southwest, New -- Description and travel.; Southwest, New -- Social conditions.; United States -- Boundaries -- Mexico.; Mexico -- Boundaries -- United States.; Southwestern States -- Description and travel.; Mexican-American Border Region -- Civilization.
Container List
- Series I: Publications by Tom Miller
  - Subseries 1: Articles
    - Wooster Represents France During Mock UN. Voice. Wooster, OH, April 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Howard Foster Lowry-1901-1967. Voice. Wooster, OH, September 22, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Sports Review Needed. Voice. Wooster, OH, November 10, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Student Demonstration Emerges from Miles Unrest. Voice, Wooster, OH, November 17, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alabama Right Paper Finds The Going Rough. Voice. Wooster, OH; Commentary: 4, February 23, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Grad School Wipeout. Voice. Wooster, OH, February 23, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - A big zero: The Chicago Literary Review; 5(4): 1, 10. Review of How to End the Draft: The Case for a Voluntary Army, March 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Wooster Students Raise $600 To Keep Favorite Professor. The Billboard. Wilson College, Chambersberg, PA., March 1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bev Asbury Wows Wooster. The Vanderbilt Hustler; Note: guest column. Voice. Wooster, OH, March 12, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Drushal Selected Eighth Wooster President; Role of Community Gov't, Church Assessed. Voice. Wooster, OH, April 19, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - New HEW Secretary Wilbur Cohen Calls For Mobilization of US Vitality. Wooster Daily Record. Wooster, OH, April 27, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - New Student And College Aid Plans Seen By HEW Head (Cohen Interview). Wooster Daily Record. Wooster, OH, April 30, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Whatever Happened to Judge Crater? Shaft, May 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Columbian Proportions. And, In Tuesday's Primary Voice. Wooster, OH, May 3, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Chicago '68: That Old Camaraderie (The 'Movement' Breaks Free). The Hatchet. George Washington University, September 19, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - S.D.S. to Rap J. Edgar Hoover. Chalkdust. Boston State, Fall 1968 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Wallace, Halstead-Boutelle Show Campaign Similarities. The Hatchet. George Washington University, September 30, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Where Are You Now, Judge Carter [sic]? (Dead or Alive?). The Hatchet, October 10, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lowenstein in New York. The Web. Webster College, St. Louis, MO, November 1, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - I Regret That I Have But One Shirt To Give (Hoffman Found Guilty). The Hatchet. Wooster College, November 21, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Yippie Hoffman Found Guilty of Desecrating American Flag. The Massachusetts Daily Collegian. University of Massachusetts, November 26, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - The Realist: Personal Journal of Wrongeous Indignation. The Chicago Literary Review, December 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Stars and Stripes-Forever. Washington Free Press, December 1-15, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - The Inaugural Ball, January 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - "we were the conquerors of the world". The Geneseo Lamron, February 7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Duke Students Demonstrate Southern-Style. Kentucky Kernel. Lexington, February 25, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Growing Science Research Stoppage Set For Tomorrow. The Kentucky Kernel, March 3, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - McSurleys File Suit Against Subcommittee Members. The Kentucky Kernel, March 5, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - How Students Confront The Administration At A Southern University. The Gazette and Daily. York, PA, March 10, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - President In Exile. The ISU Bengal, March 12, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Demonstrations hit role of research. The Michigan Daily. Ann Arbor, MI, March 14, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - AWOL in Nixon County. College Press Service, April 1969 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Committee Formed To Investigate Assassinations. The Gazette and Daily. York, PA, April 16, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Blast From the Past Continued, A Visit With Mothers. The Wilmington Monitor. Wilmington, April 1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - AWOL in Whittier. Hard Times, April 28-May 5 1969 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Rep. Edward Koch introduces 'second chance' draft bill. The Torch. Valparaiso, IN, May 9, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Special to the Guardian. Hisc ** Boom ** Bah! Guardian: independent radical newsweekly. New York, June 7, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Movement Vanguard. Hard Times, June 9-16, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Ruralism, Racism & Rhythm. Dallas Notes. Dallas, TX, July 2-23, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Dallas Blues. Hard Times, July 14-21, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - The Groupies of Anna. Rolling Stone, September 6, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Can This Really Be the End? Hard Times, September 8-15, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Lampoon disc spins sacred cows. Detroit News. Detroit, MI, Fall 1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - A Melting Pot at Sky River Festival. Rolling Stone, October 4, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Kill, Kill. Hard Times, November 3-10, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Right Off. Hard Times, December 1-8, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Morrison of the Doors Busted. Druid Free Press, December 10-16, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - The Border: 'Just A Routine Check'. Rolling Stone, December 27, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Festival Festival. The Butterfield Express, January 7-13, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Writer's poll. Fusion; II,36. Participant, January 20, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Abbie Hoffman strikes back. Big Fat Magazine, February 1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Arizona: YIP Rock Unplugged. Rolling Stone, February 21, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Has 007 had the biscuit? Big Fat Magazine, March 1970 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Freak Brothers Air Shut Off. Rolling Stone, March 7, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Rock and Roll's Captive Audience. Rolling Stone, March 7, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Paolo Soleri & His Arcological Cities. Rolling Stone, April 30, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - First Issue. Mad Funk. Tucson, AZ, Summer 1970 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Palo Verde Free Festival. Mad Funk. Tucson, AZ, Summer 1970 (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - This Man is Dangerous. Mad Funk. Tucson, AZ, Summer 1970 (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - POWs Need Bread. Mad Funk. Tucson, AZ, Summer 1970 (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - Yippie Flyer. Ephemera, Summer 1970 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Army Tries Good Vibes. Man Funk. Tucson, AZ, June 1970 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Law and Order in New Mexico. Rolling Stone, July 9, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - Yippie! Liberated Guardian, July 14, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Whatever Happened to Judge Crater? And Couldn't It Happen To You? Fusion, December 25, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - End of the Year Hip/Rad Show Your Colors Quiz. Fusion, January 22, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - Let a Thousand Free Stores Rise!! Dallas Notes. Dallas, TX, January 24-February 6, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - The Mad Funk Collective. Great Brown Rice Riot. Los Angeles Free Press. Los Angeles, CA, February 5, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Winter Offensive Begins in Tucson: Brown Rice Riot. Liberated Guardian, February 10, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - A cowboy saga: the legend of Billy Brooks. The ah, alternative life-style, saddle-sores and all. Fusion, February 19, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Mad Funk Collective. The House of the Rising Rent. People's News Service. Tucson, AZ, April 1971 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Repression Hits Hard...Politics Means Death for Tucson Black. Liberated Guardian, April 15, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Today's Army Wants to Join You. Liberated Guardian, July 1971 (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - Big John Cash Goes West, or, A Country & Western Showman Shown in the Western Part of the Country Unmasked. Fusion, July 9, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - we are all reporters in the courts of amerika. Berkeley Tribe. Berkeley, CA, August 27-September 1, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - The Hare Krishna Look. Creem, September 1971 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - unsigned. Tucson. Berkeley Tribe. Berkeley, CA, September 1971 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - unsigned. Tucson. Berkeley Tribe. Berkeley, CA, September 3-9, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 78)
    - The Krishna Look. Door. San Diego, CA, September 15-28, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 79)
    - The "Godhead Look". New Times. Tucson, AZ, September 29, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 80)
    - Fusion, October 15, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 81)
    - Zap, He's Gone ... Hydro?Fux Bed Electrifies TV Viewer. The Hatchet. Washington, D.C., October 28, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 82)
    - Waterbed fatality. New Times. Tucson, AZ, November 17, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 83)
    - Letter. Fusion, November 26, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 84)
    - First Waterbed Fatality. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, December 17-24, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 85)
    - The Hare Krishna Look. Hilltopper Revisited, 1971, 1972 ? (Box 1, Folder 86)
    - Kidstars Busted! Nation Shocked! Head Monthly, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 87)
    - America's First Waterbed Fatality. Fifth Estate. Detroit, MI, January 13-26, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 88)
    - The Questions: Fusion's How Green My America Quiz. Fusion, January 21, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 89)
    - Former Aide Tells All: The Real Poop on J. Edgar Hoover. Space City, March 16-22, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 90)
    - J. Edgar Hoover Sleeps with a Night Light: Former Valet Reveals FBI Chief's Secret Hangups. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, March 24-31, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 91)
    - The dialectics of an ice cream sandwich. DC Gazette. Washington, D.C., April 19, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 92)
    - Free Stores: A Way to Cash in on Community Organizing. Alternative Features Service, May 5, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 93)
    - Let a Thousand Free Stores Rise. Mockingbird. Houston, TX, June 16-30, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 94)
    - Ruby's Kitchen Sink. SunDance, August-September, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 95)
    - Ruby's Kitchen Sink. SunDance. (Copy 2), August-September, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 96)
    - Waylon Jennings: Good-Hearted Woman. Fusion, August 1972 (Box 1, Folder 97)
    - Two Votes For Roger Mudd. Fusion, October 1972 (Box 1, Folder 98)
    - Stories by Tom T. Hall. Fusion, December 1972 (Box 1, Folder 99)
    - Tucson police dope: What kind of joint is this? New Times, December 20, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 100)
    - Ozona Is the Richest. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, January 12-19, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ACLU Gets in Dig at D.C. Police. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, January 26-February 2, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Vending of America: Co-opting a 200-year-old revolution. Crawdaddy, February 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Thanks for the Spins, Deejays: Nitpicking and Shitkicking in Nashville. Creem, March 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Who really killed Lee Harvey Oswald? Crawdaddy, March 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Jurys Are Not Always Grand. Fusion, June 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Editors Lift Up Corner of Rug at Denver Confab. Berkeley Barb. Berkeley, CA, June 22-28, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Herb Kalmbach's Ultimate Mission. Straight Creek Journal. Denver, CO, August 7-14, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - A Connection. Seer's Catalog, August 15-29, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Out in the West Texas town of El Paso ... Crawdaddy, September 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - The Sun Sometimes Sets on the American Empire. Esquire, September 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Out in the West Texas town of El Paso. New Times Weekly, November 9-16, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Adolph's Used Cars: What do I hear for a 30-yr-old bulletproof Mercedes? Oui, December 1973 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Only Fourteen and Knows how to Nasty. Crawdaddy, December 1973 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - In Lieu of Flowers. Fusion (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Anniversary Investigation: Who Killed Buddy Holly? Crawdaddy, February 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Enroll Up ... for the Magical Military Tour! Crawdaddy, April 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - A Dylanesque Toast to Allende. The Boston Phoenix. Boston, MA; Boston After Dark, May 28, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Foodstamp Heaven. Fusion, July 1974 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - [More] of the Same. Fusion, August-September, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Asleep At The Wheel - Swing's Their Thing. Zoo World, August 15, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Eco-Saboteurs: Lurkers on the Corporate Threshold. Rolling Stone, August 29, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Why are we in Nashville? because there's room for everyone humming to the tune of cash registers and fine country music. In Touch, September 1974 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - One more side of R. Zimmerman. Musical Express, October 5, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Yet another side of Bob Dylan. Creem, October 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - October Is Country Music Month. Crawdaddy, October 1974 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Oh Lord, won't you buy me Hitler's Mercedes Benz?! Crawdaddy, October 1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Oh Lord, won't you buy me Hitler's Mercedes Benz?! New Times, Tucson, AZ, October 23-29, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Billy Jack Goes to Court, Or, bury my part at Old Tucson. Proof Sheet, November 1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - What Is The Sound Of One Billboard Falling? Berkeley Barb. Berkeley, CA, November 8-14, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - The Fascination with Assassination. Tucson Daily Citizen. Tucson, AZ; Ole! The Tucson Daily Citizen Magazine, November 16, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - That's Shoe Business. Seer's Catalog, November 21-December 6, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - The Politics of Earth Shoes: Volkswagens for the Feet. Iconoclast. Dallas, TX, November 22-29, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Ecology Raiders Flaunt the Law: Trail Of Destruction Is Left In The West; City Fathers Demand Immediate Action. Vandalism Reigns Supreme! The Aquarian, December 4-18, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Openers Section. Oui, January 1975 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Just Another Atrocity Tale. Berkeley Barb. Berkeley, CA, January 2, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Wraparound. Harper's Magazine Wraparound. Harper's Magazine, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Another atrocity tale (from Texas). Seer's Catalog, January 20 - February 3, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Food Conspiracy: It was a riot in the beginning. New Times. Tucson, AZ, January 22-28, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Food Conspiracy Coop. [Tom Miller Sez!]. Food Conspiracy Newsletter. Tucson, AZ, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Firesign Theater: Gravity Is The Opposite of Comedy. Seers: New Mexico's Other Newspaper, January 31 - February 14, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - 60339 Sings The Blues. Country Music, February 1975 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Airport '75: "Fly me, I'm a Narc Bagman." Crawdaddy, March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Cody and His Lost Planet Airmen. The New York Post. New York, NY, March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Fast Draw! Gunsmoke Returns To The West. Country Music, March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Roy Clark: Country Music's Top Banana. Saga, March 1975 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Didn't Lead Three Lives: A Brush with The CIA. Harper's Weekly, March 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Rolling Stone: Airmen in good shape. Dallas Times Herald. Dallas, TX, March 30, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - College Bookers Shop for Pop. Rolling Stone, April 24, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Country Music, April 1975 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Caution: Adults at Play With Guns. Tucson Daily Citizen. Tucson, AZ; Ole! The Tucson Daily Citizen Magazine, June 21, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - The Assassination Please Almanac: The Brains Behind the President. Crawdaddy, August 1975 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Growing Up Male: A Few Words by Tom Miller ... on an Exceptional Film. Rolling Stone, October 9, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Tom Miller From Tucson, Arizona. Picking Up The Tempo: a country western journal, December/January, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Karl Marx Never Wore Earth Shoes. Berkeley Barb. Berkeley, CA, January 9-15, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Firesign Theater: Gravity Is The Opposite of Comedy. Seers: New Mexico's Other Newspaper, January 31-February 14, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Strident Telegram From Scenic Desert. [letter to editor] Austin Sun, February 12-25, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Bradshaw Tries QB Sneak Through Studio. Country Music, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Remembering Phil Ochs. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, April 25, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Phil Ochs: 'It's Tough To Be Sensitive In A Parking Lot'. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, April 25, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Remembering Phil Ochs. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, April 25, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Papago Indians are Chicken Scratching... Country Music, May 1976 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Bloodshed is my Business. Rolling Stone, May 6, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Tom Miller Wants to Know What the FBI Wants to Know About Tom Miller. Tucson Daily Citizen. Tucson, AZ, June 5, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Getting Your FBI File: Send them a letter. You may learn things about yourself you never knew before! New Times. Tempe, AZ, June 23-29, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Tom Miller Wants to Know What the FBI Wants to Know About Tom Miller. Tucson Daily Citizen. Tucson, AZ, June 18-July 2, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Phoenix Homecoming. The Dallas Sun. Dallas, TX, September 1976 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - For Another Look At JFK's Death. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, December 19, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - For Another Look At JFK's Death. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ (copy 2), December 19, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Coverup lowdown. Names the names & rakes the muck. By Paul Mavrides and Jay Kinney. [comic book] Consultant, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Fort Huachuca: Where Spies Cavort. The Nation, January 29, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Cow Killers. Tucson, June 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - New Clues In JFK Plot: The Country Music Connection. Reliable Source, June-July, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Honky Tonk Music, by the Dusty Chaps. High Times, July 1977 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Rhodesian mercenaries. Zodiac News Service, August 4, 1977. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Hanigan-trial Mexicans: 'We had bad luck the day we crossed'. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, November 20, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Name-Calling in the Park. Nuestro, December 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Please buy my book. Tucson Citizen. Tucson, AZ, December 31, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Coming up in the next issue of New Times magazine. Informed Source. New York, NY, January-March 1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - The 15 Least Important Facts About the JFK Assassination. Head Monthly, March 1978 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Buy My Book. Los Angeles Free Press. Los Angeles, CA, April 3, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Merc Circ. Playboy, July 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Charlie Manson's "Family Hour": How Schwepsi-cola International blew millions of advertising bux on Charlie Manson and lived to deny it. Head Monthly, August 1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - The Right to Bear Organs. Playboy, August 1978 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Abbey's Road. New West, October 23, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Frontier Law: Open Season on Mexicans. Crawdaddy, November 1978 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Pistol Justice: White Cops and Chicano Corpses. The Nation, November 4, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Assassination Scorecard: Grassy Knoll Proves Fertile Ground for Screwball Theories. The National Opener, December 20, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - First "Tortilla Curtain" Gets Chili Reaction. Crawdaddy Feature, February 1979 (Box 3, Folder 20)